http://www.trinitywallstreet.org/privacy

Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Core Values
Core values guide us in carrying out our mission and realizing our vision.
Whole Community Learning
Children, Youth, and FamiliesChildren, Youth, and Families Overview
The Giving Tree
Global PartnersGlobal Partners OverviewAnglican Church in Africa
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us at Trinity Wall Street (“Trinity”, “we”, or “our”). Accordingly, we have established and implemented information handling practices for www.trinitywallstreet.org (the “Site”) that we believe are consistent with the highest standards and best practices of organizations doing business on the Internet. This Privacy Policy describes the practices that apply to the Site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information. We have prepared this detailed Privacy Policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions about how you use the Site. Capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy have the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms of Use.
When You Visit The Site
You can always visit the Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information. However, when you visit, we do learn your Internet Protocol address and may associate it with your record in applications such as Google Analytics and CRM (Customer Relationship Manager) software. By using your data, we can better understand, for example, how the Site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at the Site, and the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors. We may use this information to improve the Site’s Content and ease of use.
When You Correspond With Us
When you expressly provide us with your personal information, whether by sending us an email or by providing information directly to the Site by signing up for one of our programs, we may learn your name, email address, zip code and other contact information. In addition, we will learn your contact information and the amount of your gift when you donate through the Site. However, we will never have access to any credit card or other financial information you provide in connection with your donation, such information being obtained directly and used only by our third party service providers charged with managing our donations. We will take all reasonable measures to protect your contact information, and we will not share it with third parties, such as direct marketers, without your request or consent. However, you acknowledge and agree that we or our authorized agents may provide your personal information (a) to third-party providers of services to the Site, such as computer programmers and technicians, to maintain or update the Site, or to help improve the Site’s Content and ease of use, or (b) to other third parties when compelled by a court order or other legal process. With respect to (a) above, we will provide your information only to third parties that are under obligation to reasonably protect this information.
Security
The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We safeguard the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and other procedures. However, it is not possible to guarantee the security or integrity of information disclosed online. Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet, including when you are using the Site.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
We or our authorized agent may place a “cookie” or “pixel tag” on your computer when you come to the Site. These devices are small computer files that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you visit the Site. We may use these devices to collect data to help us personalize and improve your experience on the Site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. If you decide not to accept our cookies, your ability to use some features on the Site may be impaired because our computer will not automatically recognize yours.
Links to Third-Party Websites
The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site and does not cover information collected elsewhere.
California Privacy Rights
Pursuant to California Civil Code § 1798.83, a California resident who has provided personal information to a business with which he/she has established a business relationship has the right to request from that business information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom such personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed, upon receipt of a request by a California resident. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right. As noted above, we do not disclose such personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure.
Modifications to this Privacy Policy
Trinity reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices in this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason.
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by mail at Trinity Wall Street, 76 Trinity Place, New York, NY 10006, or email copyrightagent@trinitywallstreet.org.
Last updated as of December 5, 2019.
© 2016 Trinity Wall Street
